Well,
the world has wonders seven they say.
But they haven't seen your legs today.
They go on for miles like a highway line.
So smooth and silky,
lord,
they're fine.
From your pretty little ankles to your upper thighs.
They're the sweetest sight for these old eyes.
Yeah,
they're long and lovely,
sleek and strong.
I could stare at them all day long.
But,
oh,
your tiny knee caps.
They're like little bottle caps.
Just sitting there so neat and small.
They're the cutest part of all.
Yeah,
your tiny kneecaps.
Maybe they're my favorite maps.
Leading me to paradise.
Oh,
those knees are mighty nice.
When you wear those cutoffs straight at the end.
That's when my poor heart just can't pretend.
It's a masterpiece of biology.
What those lovely legs just do to me.
Some men like mountains,
some like the sea.
But your perfect stems are the view for me.
So graceful when you walk,
so fine when you stand.
The best pair of legs in all the land.
But,
oh,
your tiny knee caps.
They're like little bottle caps.
Just sitting there so neat and small.
They're the cutest part of all.
Yeah,
your tiny knee caps.
Maybe they're my favorite maps.
Leading me to paradise.
Oh,
those knees are mighty nice.
Now people write poems about your eyes.
And your lovely head and my surprise.
They can have your smile,
they can have your hands.
But only I truly understand.
The real attraction,
the main event.
It's all about your tiny knee caps.
They're like little bottle caps.
Just sitting there so neat and small.
They're the cutest part of all.
Yeah,
your tiny knee caps.
Maybe they're my favorite maps.
Leading me to paradise.
Oh,
those knees are mighty nice.
Yeah.
Those little bitty knees.
Love' em.
Mm.